Hey, Mikasa, what do you think?
Do you want to go help Eren?
I would yes.
Except, knowing what he told me,
I'm not sure if I want to or if
my blood is telling me to.
[MIKASA]
I'm an Ackerman.
My will's not my own.
Huh?
Look, Mikasa.
I think Eren made that up
to mess with your head.
No, he was on to something.
He asked if I get
headaches, and I do.
What makes you think
he was lying?
What makes me think h―
Guys. Do you actually
believe Eren wants to
stop all Eldians
from having children?
You honestly think he'd
go along with that?
It doesn't really strike me as
something Eren would want,
but I can't say that it's
more than he's willing―
Well I can say it!
He would never do that!
You don't think so?
Did you think he'd work
with Zeke and Yelena?
He's just pretending to!
Don't you see?
Eren's the one that has the Founding Titan's power,
so he doesn't need
to fight Zeke!
Things were
different when Yelena
first came to him with the plan.
There's no telling
what she might have done
if he had refused to join her.
He didn't have
any options back then!
But now, Eren has Yelena
completely convinced
that he's on her side,
and the Volunteers
have gotten him
in contact with Zeke.
He's in control.
He can use the rumbling
to protect the island!
Nobody will dare lay a hand on
Paradis for the next 50 years!
Hey. Can me and mine
head home now?
[NICOLO]
I'm really sorry.
Just hang tight for
a little longer, okay?
I've been calling Eren
a suicidal maniac
ever since we met
in the Cadet Corps.
I always knew that
shithead would lead us
straight to hell
if we gave him the chance.
But even knowing that,
I was still jealous of him.
For being cool enough to do it.
Huh?
[JEAN] It pisses me off
that I have to say this.
But it's the truth.
I'm not ready to see
Eren die just yet.
[Gasps]
Me neither. I owe
that guy a beatdown.
Marley can get
the hell back in line.
[Gasps] Let's go.
Stay close.
We're gonna get you home.
[MIKASA] If Eren's been
hiding his true intentions
from Yelena and the others,
then why'd he push us away
instead of telling us?
Whatever his real plan is.
Why would he have told me
that he hates me?
There must be a reason.
[EREN]
Hey...
If we did cross the sea
and we killed our enemies...
After that, would we
finally be free?
No. Couldn't be.
[Gasps]
Anyway, Eren and I
have both known about
your headaches
for a long time now.
My guess is that everything else
he said was made up,
and he used one
real detail to make
the rest of the story
more believable.
He couldn't tell the
truth in that situation,
but once all this is over,
we can ask him about it, okay?
[MIKASA]
Okay.
[MAGATH] Don't forget.
Willy Tybur sacrificed himself
to offer us a chance
to launch this assault.
Remember the message
he died to deliver.
At this point, the only hope
for humanity is another Helos.
A hero to save our world.
Come on, Eren.
[Scream]
Give up already.
You've lost this fight.
[Screaming]
[REINER] It's over,
we've suffered enough.
We all have
and that includes you.
[Screaming]
Why keep going?
Even now, you're forcing
yourself to struggle.
And for what?
[Yells]
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER 77A]
Galliard!
Ah, shit. He really
got me good with that one.
Eren. I just want to be
done with this.
How did I ever believe
we were the same?
Let it end, already.
[REINER]
Just... go to sleep!
[Gasps]
[EREN TITAN roaring]
[EREN yells]
[Gasps]
There he is.
[BOTH gasp]
[MAGATH]
The boy wonder has arrived.
I'm later than intended,
but what matters
is that I showed up
as promised, right?
You did well to hold out
for this long, Eren.
Now let your big brother
take care of the rest.
♪ Opening Song ♪
Zeke. Damn you!
Get me lined up with him.
I'll take out his nape!
Roger that.
[MAGATH]
Hurry up, Pieck!
I don't like our odds
in a straight
firefight with the Beast.
Too bad! I'm punishing
that traitor myself!
[PIECK TITAN]
But sir.
We'll hit the Cart
from both sides!
[JAEGERISTS]
Right!
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER 77D] It's
winding up for another throw!
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER 77E]
Take cover! Get off the roofs!
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER 77F] The
Founder's approaching the Beast!
[MARLEYAN SOLDIER 77G]
Looks like the two of them
are trying to come into contact!
Gotta stop 'em.
The two of us? What could we do?
We should focus on staying alive
and let Titans fight Titans.
We've got a battle of our own
to worry about now.
Let's move.
I'm gonna go rescue Falco.
You should head south.
Stay out of sight until
you reach the airship.
[GABI]
No, I'm going with you!
Falco saved my life
more than once,
and now, his life is in danger.
I'm supposed to be
the best in our unit,
but he's the only reason
I'm alive right now.
There's no way I could
abandon him to save my own skin!
[Knocking]
[ROEG]
Open up!
Tell us what
the hell's going on.
I am not gonna die
in this dungeon!
Let us out, now!
It seems like
Marley's attacking.
Maybe they showed up
to rescue you.
They would never send a
rescue mission for an Eldian.
We're completely
expendable to Marley.
But still, you've got a family
waiting for you
back home, right?
And you might be able to
see 'em again if you get away.
I'd try, at least.
I doubt I'm gonna
see my family again.
One scream from Zeke,
and it's all over.
I become a monster.
[NILE] I had so much
I wanted to say to my girls.
Now I'll never get to.
I'm as good as dead.
Don't move! I'll shoot!
This area is under the authority
of the Jaegerists.
I can't allow you to―
Stand down, Cadet.
You idiots are doing this
in Eren's name, aren't you?
You wanna stop us
from saving his life?
[SURMA]
No.
Open all these cells, right now!
[Gasps] Commandant Shadis!
Conny, huh? I picked
a fight with a bear.
Forget you saw me here,
all right? Just go.
[ARMIN]
Commander Pyxis! Are you okay?
Well, I haven't turned
senile quite yet.
But I've been better.
My drinking habit's
catching up with me.
[ARMIN gasps]
[PYXIS]
Everybody, listen up!
We don't have enough
ODM gear on hand
to get all of you equipped.
Outfitting all soldiers without
black armbands is priority one.
As for those of you
who happily partook
of our enemy's wine,
you'll be with me!
We're going to drive the
invaders of Paradis back!
[PARADIS SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[LOUISE]
This is nice.
It's good to be on
the same side again.
I'm glad we're fighting
towards a common goal now.
Yeah.
What're you doing?
You always wear that scarf.
[MIKASA]
Not this time.
[JEAN] The gate to Shiganshina.
They blocked it!
[YELENA] Zeke's destroyed
Marley's aerial fleet.
[YELENA]
The moment has finally arrived.
History is about to be written!
[Gasps]
[CONNY]
So, uh.
From what I can see,
Eren's doing just fine.
It's Reiner that needs help.
What the hell?
Zeke's here? But how?
Captain Levi wouldn't've
released him for anything.
There's no way!
Hey! What happened to
Levi and Hange?
[YELENA] I think we can assume
this means Zeke defeated them.
He promised to meet Eren here
and so that's what he did.
No one could've
made him break his vow.
[CONNY gasps]
No way, that's impossible.
[ARMIN] This doesn't
change the situation.
Only Zeke and Eren can
save the world right now.
The sad fact is that
we're out of options.
We have to help
the Jaegerists unite them!
Please help Eren and
Zeke as best you can.
I trust you, Armin.
[GABI]
The airships!
Damn it.
[GABI] Hey, what's with
the big metal pipe?
[COLT]
It's an Anti-Titan rifle.
Pretty tough to get
a kill with it, though.
You gotta hit the nape dead on,
and at a good angle.
[Gasps] Enemies!
It looks like
the whole city's in flames.
We've got nowhere to run.
What're you getting at?
We're here to fight!
[ALL gasp]
You see something?
Someone spotted us.
It's my brother.
I see.
All right, prisoner.
You're coming with me.
[FALCO gasps]
I'm gonna leave him tied up
in one of these houses.
Try to do it quickly.
We'll leave soon.
I've got no choice.
[GABI]
Wait!
[BOTH gasp]
This is no place for a child.
Try to get home, if you can.
[FALCO gasps]
Let's go!
Thanks for this, Mr. Nile.
They've moved on.
Gabi. What made you trust
that enemy soldier?
Huh? Well, uh...
[NICOLO] This way.
The fire's spreading fast,
but it won't reach this part
of the city for a while.
[ARTUR] It might come
and around and trap us,
but I suppose it's
worth the risk.
[NICOLO] Agreed. Let's hide here
'til the fighting stops.
[LISA]
Wonder where Ben and Mia went.
I sure hope they're okay.
[ARTUR]
I reckon they'll be just fine.
Those two're 'toughuns.
Hey, wait!
[KAYA]
I hope they die.
You might not care that
they murdered our sister,
but I won't forgive them. Ever.
They're evil.
I'd kill them myself if I could.
Looks like they're gone now.
We should get moving.
Gabi.
[GABI] There were never
any devils on this island.
Just people. People like us.
I see now. I finally get
how Reiner feels.
[GABI] We just mindlessly
agreed, that even though
we'd never met these people,
they all had to be devils.
Ever since the airship,
it's just been the same thing,
over and over again.
[GABI]
You knew, right, Falco?
You only came
to try and help me.
I'm sorry.
[FALCO] I helped cause
the massacre in Liberio.
[BOTH gasp]
I made friends
with a hurt soldier
who turned out to be
Eren Jaeger.
Not realizing who he was,
I helped him sneak
letters to his allies.
And then they attacked our home.
So yeah. Udo and Zofia
are dead because of me.
Oh, I see.
And also. I'm in love with you.
[GABI]
Huh?
Look, the truth of it is
I only became a candidate
for one reason.
To keep the Armor from you.
I wanted us to get married.
I wanted you and me
to be happy together.
I wanted to know
you'd live a long time!
Wait, why tell me this now?
Just thought I'd take
this chance to say my piece.
Now, before I turn Titan.
[BOTH gasp]
[Gasps]
Let's go!
Zeke likes you,
so we should let him know
you drank his spinal fluid.
Think that might convince him
not to use his scream.
[FALCO]
Yeah.
[JEAN]
It's no use! There're too many!
We can't get to Eren!
[JEAN gasps]
[ZEKE TITAN]
Eren. We're so close.
A few more steps and we'll
have made our dream come true.
Just keep moving.
What's that?
[ZEKE]
The Cart Titan.
So that's where my dear
little Pieck met her end.
Yeah! We got the Cart Titan!
We finally managed to
catch up to you guys.
Who finished her off?
Huh? We thought one of
you took her out.
[KOSLOW]
Shoot! Kill 'em all!
The trick we just pulled
will only earn you one shot.
Make it count, General.
Could that have done it?
This angle's no good!
Move closer!
[MARLEYAN COMMANDER 77A]
Braun!
You can't let the Founder
reach the Beast!
[REINER]
Still stumbling forward, huh?
Just stop already.
[REINER]
The last person in the world
who should have
that power... is you.
Eren.
Hurry up! Get a move on!
If he's got so much as
an ounce of life left,
he's gonna scream.
♪ Ending Song ♪
[NARRATOR]
Beast and Founder.
The battle comes to a head
as both sides rush
to attack and defend
these two key Titans.
What will the brothers find
at the end of their path?
Next episode: "Two Brothers."